In lecture, Dave pointed out that these 2 functions,
在演讲中 Dave 指出这两个函数
hashtable_update and hashtable_lookup,
hashtable-update 和 hashtable-lookup
use some similar functionality
使用一些类似的功能
that instead we could place in a separate procedure.
我们可以把它放在一个单独的程序里
Looking at the hashtable_update and lookup procedures here,
看看这里的 hashtable-update 和 lookup 程序
we see code that's identical between them, namely these 2 lines.
我们看到这些代码完全相同 就是这两行
In both functions, these 2 lines of code go through a given bucket
在这两个函数中 这两行代码走遍了指定的“桶”
searching for an entry whose first value is the key.
搜寻第一个值等于 key 的项目
And so what we're going to do is we're going to take this code
所以我们要做的是 取得这段代码
and move it into a separate helper function.
将其移到一个单独的 helper 函数
This is known as refactoring.
这称为重构 (refactoring)
Refactoring is a common software engineering practice
重构 (refactoring) 是常见的软体工程实践 (practice)
where we change the code without changing the functionality.
我们改变了代码 但是没有更改功能
There's a number of reasons to do so.
这么做有一些原因
For example, here we're doing it to minimize duplicated code.
例如 在这里我们是为了尽量减少重复的代码
This is desirable, because if we want to change how these 2 lines of code work--
这令人满意 因为如果我们想要改变 这两行代码运作的方式
perhaps we change the structure of the bucket--
或许我们改变了“桶”的结构
we don't want to look through every hash table function
我们不想看遍每个哈希表函数
searching for how this works and updating them.
搜寻这是如何运作的 并且更新它们
Rather, we just want to update it in 1 place.
而我们只是想要在一个地方做更新
This minimizes bugs and saves time. So let's give it a try.
这减少了臭虫 (bug) 而且节省时间  现在 让我们试一试
Here I've created a new function called bucket_find.
这里我建了一个新函数 称为 bucket-find
You should see that it's very similar to the code that we have in update and lookup
你应该看到它与 update 和 lookup 的代码非常相似
in that we're going to go through the bucket searching for the entry
在这里 我们要走遍“桶”来搜寻项目
whose first value is the key and then returning the entire entry
项目中第一个值等于 key 然后传回整个项目
so that we can use it accordingly in both update and lookup.
因此我们可以在 update 和 lookup 使用它
So now that we have the helper function, let's change our hash table functions to use it.
现在有了 helper 函数  让我们使用它来改变我们的哈希表函数
The resulting code is going to be both simpler and shorter.
产生的代码会变得更简单也更短
I've changed hashtable_update.
我已经改变了 hashtable-update
We find the bucket in the first line,
我们在第一行找到了“桶”
then within the bucket we're searching for the key,
然后在“桶”里 我们要搜寻 key
and if we find that entry we're going to update the value.
如果找到了这个项目 我们要更新值
Otherwise we're going to append the key and the value to the end of the bucket.
否则我们要把 key 和 value 加到“桶”的末尾
It looks quite a bit simpler than the original function.
它看起来比原始函数来的简单
Let's do the same thing to lookup.
让我们对 lookup 做同样的事
In the new hashtable_lookup, we first find the bucket
在新的 hashtable-lookup 我们首先找到“桶”
and then within the bucket we search for the entry.
然后在“桶”里 我们搜寻项目
If the entry is not None, we return the second value.
如果这个项目不是 None 我们传回第二个值
Otherwise we return None.
否则我们传回 None